MAAZ NAVEED

E: maaznaveed1999@gmail.com

P: +92-3138949530

L: https://www.linkedin.com/in/maaznaveedkhan/

A: Multan

SKILLS

Laravel

Html

Css

Bootstrap

Python

Jquery

HOBBIES

- Cricket
- Reading Books
- Social Media
- Learning a new skill

LANGUAGES

Urdu

English

PROFILE

Working as a Laravel Developer. I also work on frontend designs. I love to work on Python. Developed many projects based on Laravel. I have also written a Python script. I also made a Web scrapper using Python. Worked on some International Projects.

EDUCATION

BS Computer Science | NCBA&E, Multan

Nov 2017 - Oct 2021

Intermediate | Muslim College, Multan

Jul 2017 - Jul 2017

Matriculation | Italian School, Multan

Jun 2013 - Jun 2015

EXPERIENCE

Laravel Developer | NextStep Solutions, Multan

May 2022 - Present

- Learning new things everyday.
- Working on projects in group and sole

Intern | Eusopht, Karachi

Dec 2021 - Apr 2022

- Built and maintained websites for International Clients
- Learnt lot's of tools & technologies
- A career defining opportunity to work there

RELEVANT PROJECTS

Some Projects are given below

https://www.broadbandmarket.com/

https://aashercollection.com/

http://intrapidusconsulting.co.uk/

https://edrugs.pk/

https://theclci.com/

https://evalu.ca/

https://virtualgettogather.com/

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Dawn National Spelling Bee | Multan

Feb 2014

Words Spell competition organized by Dawn and US Embassy

CERTIFICATIONS

CPA Programming Essentioials | Cisco

Jul 2018